https://nakamalathome.com/privacy-policy

Home
ShopSALE
Kava
Stone KavaWow KavaTrue KavaFire Island Instant KavaBlack Sand KavaSolomon KavaWhite Sand KavaKava Powder Sample PackKava Beverage
Preparation
Kava Preparation BagsKava Recipe Fiji StyleKava Recipe Vanuatu Syle
My Account
Wish List (0)
Kava
Stone KavaWow KavaTrue KavaFire Island Instant KavaBlack Sand KavaSolomon KavaWhite Sand KavaKava Powder Sample PackKava Beverage
Preparation
Kava Preparation BagsKava Recipe Fiji StyleKava Recipe Vanuatu Syle
0 / $0.00
Your shopping cart is empty!
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Statement InformationNakamal@HOME (collectively referred to in this Privacy Statement as "we" or "Nakamal") recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by customers at our retail stores, users of our web sites, recipients of our e-mail newsletters and all of our on-line customers. We created this policy with a fundamental respect for our users' right to privacy and to guide our relationships with our users. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for all products and services.Information Nakamal gathers and tracksNakamal gathers three types of information about users:Data users provide through optional, voluntary registration on our sites,Data users provide through purchasing any of our products or services at our retail stores and web, andAggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. Such information enables us to better tailor our content to readers' needs, quickly and efficiently process purchase orders and help us better understand the demographics of our audience.Nakamal does not provide any information to any third parties under any circumstances, unless it is need to securely process any purchases using a credit card. Information such as account name, number and expiration date, is used for billing purposes only, and is not otherwise shared. We do not store any credit card information on any of our systems. Nakamal uses SkipJack Internet Merchant Account Services for secure and reliable credit card processing for all our on-line purchase transactions. For more about SkipJack, please visit them at SkipJack.com.Questions regarding this statement should be directed here: info@nakamalathome.com.Disclosure Of Information In Public AreasIf you voluntarily disclose information in a public area of a Nakamal web site, such as a chat room or message board, that information may be collected and used by a third party to send you unsolicited messages, advertisements or for other purposes. We do not control the actions of these third parties in public areas of a Nakamal site, so if you disclose information in a public area, you do so at your own risk.No Absolute SafeguardsAlthough we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control.Electronic NewslettersNakamal offers occasional, free electronic newsletters to users. This newsletter is sent on a limited number of occasions, usually to announce specials, events, or kava industry news. Nakamal gathers the e-mail addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Customers may remove themselves from any mailing list by following the instructions contained in every newsletter.SurveysNakamal occasionally conducts customer surveys to better target our content and product inventory to our audience. We never share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with third parties. We never share any information about specific individuals with any third party, except as noted previously.Contests and giveawaysNakamal offers contests and sweepstakes in which we request certain personal information. These contests and sweepstakes are conducted in full accordance with United States federal and state laws. The full rules and all information about such contests are clearly posted during such events. Information gathered is used only to verify user identity and to contact winners and/or prize recipients, except when specifically noted otherwise. Again, we do not share information about specific individuals with any third party, except as noted previously.Usage trackingNakamal tracks user traffic patterns throughout Nakamal and this information is correlated with data about individual users. Overall usage statistics, according to a user's domain name, browser type and MIME type gotten by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser), are also broken down.Nakamal also tracks and catalogs the search terms that customers enter into our search tools, but this tracking is never associated with individual users.CookiesA cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such including a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Nakamal uses cookies to track the items you add to your shopping card and to enforce security rules regarding software that you download.If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie.You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. However, you need to have cookies turned on to purchase software through NakamalAtHome.com.Use of the informationNakamal uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.As stated above, Nakamal uses information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and enable users to participate in polls and message boards. We send out newsletters to subscribers on a occasion when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Nakamal never shares newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers or partners.We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. Nakamal does not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.We track search terms entered in our search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.Nakamal creates aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. Nakamal never shares individual personal information with anyone, so an advertiser will never know that a specific user clicked their ad.Nakamal uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience demographics. We do not share information about individual users with any third party, with the exceptions noted previously.Acceptance of Privacy StatementIf you use a Nakamal web site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Statement, and we will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Statement, you must discontinue use of the Nakamal web site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. Your continued use of a Nakamal web site after we either personally notify you or generally post such changes on the web site will constitute your acceptance of those changes.Opt-Out PolicyNakamal gives users options wherever necessary and practical, such choices include:Opting not to receive our electronic newsletters when registering for a siteOpting not to provide certain personal information when registering for a site or serviceOpting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need for any information from our usersUnsubscribe PolicyUsers may unsubscribe to any of our electronic newsletters at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of each newsletter.How To Contact UsIf you ever need to contact us via email, e-mail us at info@nakamalathome.com.
Facebook
Twitter
Instagram
Youtube
Information
About Us
Refund Policy
Privacy Policy
Importer of Kava direct from the source. Farm to shell.
1723 Avenida Del Sol Boca Raton, FL 33432
Phone: 888-572-KAVA (5282)
© Copyright NAKAVA LLC - All rights reserved. 2010 - 2020
